Guide to the Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust Collection 1938-[1970-1998] 2000
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
- Series II: A.H. Robins Litigation Documents
  - Sub-series 1: AHR Employee Depositions and Testimony
    - Sub-sub-series 2: Non-MDL Depositions
      Also, Frank William Mann, Jr., A. Edwin Martin, Joseph Mazzeo, Thomas J. McCarthy III, William D. McGehee, Otto McGilvrey, Allen Arthur McKeel, Olivia McMichael, James Gray McWhorter, David Mefford, James Frederick Miller, Clyde Moore, Kenneth E. Moore, Emily M. Morley, C.E. Morton, Dr. Robert S. Murphey, James M. Nisely, Edward Normandia, Terry G. Oakley, Roy Francis O'Hanley, Jr., Guy Edward O'Neal, John P. Onkey, Dr. Fletcher B. Owen, Jr., Jerry Paul Parker, William B. Plisco, Allen J. Polon, Dr. Ellen J. Preston, Dr. Lester W. Preston, Roscoe E. Puckett, Jr., Robert Lee Ramsay, E.C. Robins, Jr., E. Claiborne Robins, Sr., Julian Ross, Phillip Rudine, Raymond J. Russo, Carroll L. Saine, Philip J. Schmid, Walt W. Schoenberger, Stephen I. Schwartz, Thomas A. Schwartz, Leland Schweer, Stuart Shumate, Michael Silva, George Smith, Louis L. Smith, W. Roy Smith, William Smithdeal, Elmer A. Snyder, Sam Sparks, Hunter Spencer, George Stiles, Arthur M. Stranz, Stephen Richard Stubbs, Robert Walker Tankersley, August Tassan, Dr. Howard Tatum, Dale R. Taylor, John Trippe, Roger Lewis Tuttle, William S. Van Bezey, Richard A. Velz, Harris Wagenseil, John W. Ward, Robert Watts, Dale E. Weiss, James C. White, William T. Yale, Alan Young, Roland Younglin, and William L. Zimmer III.
      These depositions were taken between 1975 and 1985. The transcripts, available on microfilm reels 55-82, are arranged alphabetically by deponent, and then by case name. Exhibits are sometimes included. An index precedes the documents on the microfilm.
    - Sub-sub-series 3: Trial Testimony
      Bradley Post helped the Trust select a number of cases for which the AHR company employees' trial testimony was particularly useful, and these documents became part of the Document Depository. The collection of trial testimony, available on microfilm reels 82-139, was divided in two groups arranged alphabetically by plaintiff's name.
      The first collection of testimony is for the following plaintiffs' trials: Kyle Askeland, Delma R. Barnes and Debra Jean Clark, Marguerite Bryson, Consuella Bundy, Candyce L. Cabe, Nancy S. Carley, Colorado Consolidated, or Janette A. Hawkinson, et al., Valerie Dembrosky, Susan L. Dodge, Marsha Feldman, Susan Fitzpatrick, Laureen Ford, Laurie Jo Franz, Kay Hamilton, Gay Lynn Hertzler, Linda Johnson, Terri Johnson, Patrick Junkin, Nancy Kaye, Nancy Lewis, Carole Mansfield, Jayne Miller, Gayle McCann, Joan Price, Karen Clark Raine, Carol Ann Setter, Kim Elizabeth Shewan, Joyce A. Smith, Kay E. Swenson, Robert C. and Deborah Terhune, Rosemary Warner, Francis G. Williams, and Anna Wilkins.
      The second collection of testimony is for the following plaintiffs' trials: Carin Linn Abramson, Miriam Breyer, Linda S. James Brown, Pamela Craig, Connie L. Deemer, Mary Ann Ducharme, Cynthia and Robert Fletzin, Mary Guenther, Martha E. Hahn, Linda and William Harre, Diane Hilliard, Regina and Keith Husbands, Cathy J. Maguire, Peggy Joan Mample, Sue and Wayne Mitchell, Rosalie Nunley, Carie M. Palmer, Janet and George Reif, Debbie Rohl, Elizabeth Rubin, Brenda Happke-Strempke, Loretta L. Tetuan, Pamela Van Duyn, and Sharon Worsham.
      The transcripts, having come from a variety of courts, vary a good bit, but for each case it is easy to determine whose testimony is where.
    - Sub-sub-series 4: Depositions and Trial Testimony (videotape)
      The Trust had a large collection of videotaped depositions (51 videotapes) and trial testimony (177 videotapes) of AHR employees. They transferred to the library all the tapes on VHS format. Many of these tapes, dating from 1979 to 1985, have corresponding transcripts in the previous three sub-series, but some do not.
      - Sub-sub-sub-series I: MDL Depositions
      - Elderin Wayne Crowder 1981 March, Videotape (Othertype V2-7)
      - Oscar Klioze 1983 January, Videotape (Othertype V8-10)
      - A. Edwin Martin 1983 April, Videotape (Othertype V11-12)
      - Kenneth Moore 1982 September; 1983 January, Videotape (Othertype V13-29)
      - Dr. Fletcher B. Owen, Jr. 1983 April, Videotape (Othertype V30-46)
      - Robert Walker Tankersley n.d., Videotape (Othertype V47-52)
      - Sub-sub-sub-series 2: Trial Testimony
      - Dr. Karlis Adamson (Happke-Strempke v. AHR) 1983 March, Videotape (Othertype V53-55)
      - Dr. [Samuel] Barr (Jobe v. AHR) 1985 July, Videotape (Othertype V56-57)
      - Dr. [Onofre P.] Carrillo (Jobe v. AHR) 1985 May, Videotape (Othertype V58)
      - Dr. Fred A. Clark Jr., (Cameron v. AHR) 1983 January (Othertype V59-78)
      - Dr. Fred A. Clark Jr., (Junkermeier v. AHR) 1984 January, Videotape (Othertype V79-88)
      - Dr. Fred A. Clark, Jr. (Mample v. AHR) 1983 January, Videotape (Othertype V89-91)
      - E. Wayne Crowder (Hawkinson v. AHR) 1981 May, Videotape (Othertype V92-94)
      - Dr. Thad J. Earl (Palmer v. AHR) 1979 May, Videotape (Othertype V95-98)
      - Dr. Max Elstein (Happke-Strempke v. AHR) 1983 May, Videotape (Othertype V99-101)
      - William Forrest Jr., (Junkermeier v. AHR) 1984 February, Videotape (Othertype V102-117)
      - Robert Gorvette (Happke-Strempke v. AHR) 1983 April- May, Videotape (Othertype V118-123)
      - Dr. [Louis] Keith (Happke-Strempke v. AHR) 1983 May, Videotape (Othertype V124-129)
      - Patricia Lashley (Bonlender v. AHR) 1984 August, Videotape (Othertype V130-131)
      - Dr. Daniel Mishell (Miller v. AHR) 1983 February, Videotape (Othertype V132-135)
      - Dr. Daniel Mishell [case not identified, may be Miller] [1983 February?], Videotape (Othertype V136)
      - Kenneth Moore (Bondlender v. AHR) 1984 August, Videotape (Othertype V137-138)
      - Dr. David Ostergard (Bryson v. AHR) 1985 February, Videotape (Othertype V139-140)
      - Fletcher Owen (Happke-Strempke v. AHR) 1983 March, Videotape (Othertype V141-147)
      - Fletcher Owen (Bonlender v. AHR) 1984 August, Videotape (Othertype V148-153)
      - Dr. Ellen Preston (Abril v. AHR) 1981 September, Videotape (Othertype V149-174)
      - Dr. Ellen Preston (Junkermeier v. AHR) 1984 January, Videotape (Othertype V175-186)
      - Sam Sparks (Jobe v. AHR) 1985 July, Videotape (Othertype V187-188)
      - Dr. Richard Soderstrom (Happke-Strempke v. AHR) 1983 May, Videotape (Othertype V189-191)
      - Brian Strom (Palmer v. AHR) 1985 May, Videotape (Othertype V192-193)
      - Dr. Howard Tatum (Davis v. AHR) 1984 January, Videotape (Othertype V194-199)
      - Roger Tuttle (Bonlender v. AHR) 1984 August, Videotape (Othertype V200-211)
      - Roger Tuttle (Punitive Damages) 1985 May, Videotape (Othertype V212-216)
      - Robert Watts (Happke-Strempke v. AHR) 1983 May, Videotape (Othertype V221)
      - Dr. Joe Williamson (Jobe v. AHR) 1985 May, Videotape (Othertype V222)
      - William Zimmer (Bonlender v. AHR) 1984 August, Videotape (Othertype V223-229)
  - Sub-series 2: Miscellaneous Trial Material
    This collection of trial material, 9 boxes (3.75 linear feet), was created by Trust employees for use in litigation. Included are copies of pre-trial orders, exhibits, depositions, and videotapes of depositions (33 videotapes). For Robins litigation, McGuire, Woods had prepared a set of exhibits, and so the Trust prepared their own based upon the law firm's set.
    - MDL Pre-Trial Order 1977, 1979, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Various MDL Orders 1981-1983 (Box 1)
    - Various Orders 1983-1984 (Box 1)
    - Eight Circuit Investigation of Judge Miles Lord 1984 (Box 1)
    - "5000 Series" [AHR] Exhibit List 1984 November (Box 1)
    - AHR Dalkon Shield Trial Results-List of Cases Tried to Judgment n.d. (Box 2)
    - Robins, Zelle Catalog of Materials compiled and developed by its Dalkon Shield team [mid-1980s] (Box 2)
    - Trust Standard Designation Exhibit List 1995 (Box 2)
    - Standard Trust Designations: edited portions of depositions and testimonies of Wayne Crowder (MDL), William Forrest (Bonlender), Emanuel Friedman (Healey), Patricia Lashley (Bonlender), Albert Martin (MDL), Kenneth Moore (Bonlender and MDL), Fletcher Owen (MDL), Ellen J. Preston (Abril) 1981-1997, 16 folders (Box 2)
      [videotapes of the edited depositions and testimonies are also available]
    - Standard Trust Designations, continued: edited portions of depositions and testimonies of Sam Sparks (Jobe), Roger Tuttle (Bonlender and Punitive Damages Litigation), and Russel J. Thomsen (Marshall and Bookout) 1975-1994, 6 folders (Box 3)
      [videotapes of Sparks and Tuttle also available]
    - Interrogatory Exhibits dating from 1996 to 1985 1985 June, 29 folders (Box 4-9)
    - Videotape Inventory
      - Wayne Crowder MDL Deposition-Edited Portions 1981 March (Othertype V230-231)
      - William Forrest Testimony in Bonlender- Edited Portions 1984 August (Othertype V232)
      - Dr. Emanual Friedman Deposition in Horne-Edited Portions 1997 April (Othertype V233-234)
      - Patricia Lashley Deposition in Bonlender-Edited Portions 1984 August (Othertype V235)
      - Dr. Albert Martin MDL Deposition-Edited Portions 1983 April (Othertype V236-237)
      - Kenneth Moore MDL Deposition-Edited Portion 1982 September (Othertype V238-240)
      - Kenneth Moore Deposition in Bonlender-Edited Portions 1984 August (Othertype V241)
      - Dr. Fletcher B. Owen MDL Deposition-Edited Portions 1983 (Othertype V242)
      - Dr. Ellen J. Preston Deposition in Abril-Edited Portions 1981 September & October (Othertype V243-246)
      - Sam Sparks Deposition in Jobe-Edited Portions 1985 July (Othertype V247)
      - Roger L. Tuttle Deposition in Punitive Damages Litigation 1985 May (Othertype V249-251)
      - Dr. Janet Daling Deposition in Cloutier v. DSCT 1993 July (Othertype V252-254)
      - Dr. Richard Sorce Deposition in Rendulic v. DSCT 1993 March (Othertype V255-256)
      - Dr. Emanuel Friedman Deposition in Horne v. DSCT 1997 April (Othertype V257-262)
- Series III: U.S. Food and Drug Administration Investigation of the Dalkon Shield
  This series of U.S. Food and Drug Administration files is comprised of 5 boxes (2.1 linear feet). During 1974 the FDA held several hearings investigating IUDs and septic abortions, and, specifically, the safety of the Dalkon Shield. In preparation for these investigations the agency asked AHR to present documents concerning production of their IUD. The documents the company provided make up part of this series. (Most, if not all of these documents, are also found in the Source Files.) Also included here are transcripts of various hearings. In 1983 the FDA received a request under the Freedom of Information Act to produce documents relating to AHR and the Dalkon Shield. Copies of those documents are also in this series.
  - Index of FDA Submissions related to the Dalkon Shield (Box 1)
  - FDA Requested Information on the Dalkon Shield 1973-1974, 5 folders (Box 1-2)
  - Materials Submitted to FDA 1970-1973, 4 folders (Box 2)
  - FDA Open Hearing Transcript 1974 August 21, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - AHR's Report for the FDA Obstetrics and Gynecology Advisory Committee 1974 October 22 (Box 3)
  - Ad Hoc Advisory Committee Meeting-Transcript and Report 1974 October 29-30 (Box 3)
  - Transcript of Sen. Edward Kennedy's Hearing on IUDs [Subcommittee on Health of the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare] 1975 January 28 (Box 3)
  - FDA Documents [re Dalkon Shield] Produced Pursuant to a Freedom of Information Act Request [in 1983]; with Chronological Index 1968-1983, 6 folders (Box 4-5)
- Series IV: News Materials Concerning Dalkon Shield
  This series is comprised of newspaper clippings in 9 boxes (3.75 linear feet) and videotapes of television shows concerning Dalkon Shield injuries and litigation. The clippings, dated 1974-1985, are arranged alphabetically by state and are preceded by an index.
  - Index for Collected Articles Concerning the Dalkon Shield, by State, 1974-1985 n.d. (Box 1)
  - Alabama 1974-1985 (Box 1)
  - Alaska 1973-1985 (Box 1)
  - California 1973-1985, 4 folders (Box 1-2)
  - Colorado 1974-1985 (Box 2)
  - Connecticut 1974-1985 (Box 2)
  - Delaware 1974-1985 (Box 2)
  - District of Columbia 1973-1985, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Florida 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Georgia 1974-1985 (Box 3)
  - Idaho 1974-1985 (Box 3)
  - Hawaii 1972-1985 (Box 3)
  - Illinois 1973-1985, 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Indiana 1974-1985 (Box 3)
  - Iowa 1974-1985 (Box 4)
  - Kansas 1974-1985 (Box 4)
  - Kentucky 1974-1985 (Box 4)
  - Louisiana 1974-1985 (Box 4)
  - Maine 1974-1986 (Box 4)
  - Maryland 1974-1985 (Box 4)
  - Massachusetts 1973-1985 (Box 4)
  - Michigan 1974-1985 (Box 4)
  - Minnesota 1974-1985, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Mississippi 1974-1985 (Box 5)
  - Missouri 1974-1985 (Box 5)
  - Montana 1974-1985 (Box 5)
  - Nebraska 1974-1986 (Box 5)
  - Nevada 1974-1985 (Box 5)
  - New Hampshire 1975-1980 (Box 5)
  - New Jersey 1974-1985 (Box 6)
  - New Mexico 1974-1984 (Box 6)
  - New York 1973-1986, 3 folders (Box 6)
  - North Carolina 1974-1985 (Box 6)
  - North Dakota 1974-1985 (Box 7)
  - Ohio 1973-1984, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Oklahoma 1973-1985 (Box 7)
  - Oregon 1975-1985 (Box 7)
  - Pennsylvania 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Rhode Island 1974-1985 (Box 7)
  - South Carolina 1974-1985 (Box 8)
  - South Dakota 1974-1985 (Box 8)
  - Tennessee 1974-1985 (Box 8)
  - Texas 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Utah 1974-1985 (Box 8)
  - Vermont 1974-1985 (Box 8)
  - Virginia 1973-1985, 3 folders (Box 8-9)
  - Washington 1970-1980 (Box 9)
  - Wisconsin 1974-1986 (Box 9)
  - Wyoming 1974-1985 (Box 9)
  - West Virginia 1974-1985 (Box 9)
  - Africa 1980 (Box 9)
  - Australia 1972-1984 (Box 9)
  - Belgium 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Canada 1974-1988 (Box 9)
  - France 1985 (Box 9)
  - Puerto Rico 1974-1985 (Box 9)
  - United Kingdom 1979-1985 (Box 9)
  - Virgin Islands 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Transcripts of "60 Minutes" Dalkon Shield story [aired twice] 1981 April 19 and 1984 August 5 (Box 9)
  - Transcript of "Northwest Reports with Lars Larson" on the Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust 1994 May 31 (Box 9)
  - Videotape Inventory
    - "60 Minutes" story on the Dalkon Shield, Mike Wallace narrating 1981 April 19, 2 copies (Othertype V263-264)
    - "60 Minutes" reprise of the Dalkon Shield story shown with a 1984 November 11 story on Judge Miles Lord, Mike Wallace narrating 1984 August 4, 4 copies (Othertype V265-268)
    - "60 Minutes" story on Judge Miles Lord 1984 November 11, 4 copies (Othertype V269)
    - "People are Talking" [a talk show in San Francisco], featuring Morton Mintz and Carol Hewitt 1986 [January or February] (Othertype V270)
    - "Northwest Reports with Lars Larson" on Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust, Portland, Oregon 1994 May 31 (Othertype V271)
- Series V: In re A. H. Robins; Case No. 85-01307-R
  AHR filed for federal bankruptcy protection on August 21, 1985. The Trust kept on file each pleading that was entered in the case up through August of 2000. This series contains those pleadings. In addition, there is data on some of the lawsuits Robins resolved before bankruptcy. This data was studied by analyst Frances McGovern whose report is also included. Finally, there are transcripts of the estimation hearings.
  - Sub-series 1: Docket Books
    The docket books for the AHR bankruptcy case contain, in order of filing, virtually all the pleadings entered between 1985 and 2000. In addition to the pleadings themselves in 416 three-ring notebooks (123 linear feet), there is a complete list of the documents providing the date each item was entered, its docket number, and the document's heading. Researchers must examine the list to determine the notebook-location of documents. Many of these documents also appear in other parts of the collection.
  - Sub-series 2: Resolved Cases Database
    This series of 28 boxes (22.5 linear feet) is contains data derived from a sampling of cases A. H. Robins settled before bankruptcy proceedings began. In 1976 AHR created a Product Litigation System (PLS) to assist their lawyers in tracking Dalkon Shield claims and law suits. The master file in this database included the following information about a claim: claimant name; type of action; status of action; filing and resolution dates; insurance (Aetna) information; location of litigation; information about counsel; and resolution amounts.
    About ten years later, during the claims estimation phase of the bankruptcy proceedings, AHR was asked to provide information on settled suits to assist in determining the company's liability for outstanding claims. By that time the PLS database held information on 9,500 resolved cases, of which 1,800 were selected for analysis. According to Francis McGovern, the court-appointed master of the study, the selection included 1,600 cases chosen at random, plus "a stratified sample" of the one hundred lowest and one hundred highest cases.
    This new arrangement of resolved cases data presented eight categories of information: 1. Case Summary, which contained the master file data outlined above. 2. Dalkon Shield Use, providing basic information about use and type of injury. 3. Other Contraceptive Use, including dates and type. 4. Economic Damages, listing costs incurred by the claimant including work loss. 7. Statute of Limitation including date of claim, onset of injury, first consultation with attorney, state of residence. 8. Sexual History, including names of partners and dates of relationship. This information was followed by a medical history arranged by date and including information about symptoms, procedures performed, test and results.
    In addition to the resolved cases, the McGovern study also involved analysis of questionnaires sent to about 6,000 claimants with pending claims. See Series VI Sub-series 1 Boxes 15-17 for a copy of the questionnaire along with additional information about the McGovern study.
    The print-outs of the Resolved Cases Database are bound in twenty-six oversize volumes in Boxes 1-26. The names of the claimants and their partners have been obliterated, in order to protect their privacy. The volumes are open to research without restriction. Boxes 27 and 28 contain a copy of McGovern's final report titled Report of the Dalkon Shield Claims' Estimation Process, June 15, 1988.
  - Sub-series 3: Estimation Hearing and Disclosure Statement
    From November 5 to 11, 1987, Judges Merhige and Shelley held hearings at which the various interested parties presented their estimates of the dollar value of the outstanding claims. Each party had hired experts to examine the data McGovern had compiled, and the work of these experts was presented at the hearing. Thomas Florence conducted the analysis and prepared the estimation for AHR. Other estimates were presented on behalf of the claimants' committee, Aetna, the official committee representing AHR shareholders, and the unsecured creditors. One month later Judge Merhige, having reviewed the estimates which ranged from $1.2 to 7.2 billion, announced that AHR's liability to claimants was $2.475 billion.
    On February 1, 1988, American Home Products agreed to acquire AHR, and on March 28, 1988 Robins filed its Sixth Amended and Restated Disclosure Statement Pursuant to Section 1125 of the Bankruptcy Code. This document begins with a summary of the case and a detailed overview of the settlement, followed by the Plan of Reorganization, the Claimants Trust and Other Claimants Trust Agreements, the Claims Resolution Facility, the Merger Agreement, and other documents. Along with letters of endorsement, relevant court orders and notices, and a ballot, the Disclosure Statement was mailed to all eligible claimants to vote on approval of the plan in late April 1988.
    This sub-series of 4 boxes and 1 carton (2.9 linear feet) contains the transcript of the hearing, Thomas Florence's estimation report, AHR memoranda on statute of limitations filed with the court at the time of estimation, and a copy of the disclosure statement with accompanying letters of endorsement, court orders and notices.
    - In Re: A. H. Robins: Estimation Hearing Transcripts 1987 November 5-11 (Box 1-2)
    - Report of B. Thomas Florence on behalf of AHR at the Estimation Hearing [labeled Plaintiff's Exhibits 1-99] [1987], 6 folders (Box 2-3)
    - Memorandum of A.H. Robins Regarding Statute of Limitations and Estimation of Dalkon Shield Claims 1987 November 2, 4 folders (Box 4)
    - In Re: A.H. Robins: Sixth Amended and Restated Disclosure Statement Pursuant to Section 1125 of the Bankruptcy Code (Box 4)
- Series VI: Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust Central Records Library
  The Dalkon Shield Claimants Trust opened in early 1988 with the appointment of five trustees, Barbara Blum, Kenneth Feinberg, Gene Locks, Stephen Saltzburg, and Ann Samani. The critical issue of how the Trust would be managed proved as controversial as most other aspects of the bankruptcy settlement. Consequently, within months disputes caused the resignations of Blum, Samani, and Locks. One of the new appointees, Georgene Vairo, eventually became chair of the Trust and remained in that post until it closed.
  Meanwhile the trustees hired Michael Sheppard, clerk of the bankruptcy court in Richmond, as executive director of the Trust. Others administrators hired shortly thereafter included Teri Lovelace and Ann Peters. At its peak the Trust employed a staff of almost four hundred. The staff included attorneys to handle the anticipated legal issues. General Counsel, Linda Thomason, was assisted by a team consisting of Lynn Greer, Susan Manardo, and Patricia Powis whose job was to oversee and coordinate representation of the Trust in cases that went to arbitration or litigation. Richmond lawyers Michael W. Smith and Orran L. Brown were hired as outside counsel. The legal department grew along with the caseload. Assisting the Trust staff were attorneys chosen in regions throughout the U.S., and in other countries, as required to handle local litigation. In addition, local defense attorneys were hired on a case-by-case basis when a claim went to arbitration or litigation.
  The papers of the Trust include the Central Records Library (CRL), the official staff files which document the innumerable mailings to claimants, claims processing, and other Trust administrative matters, as well as the Trustees' minutes. Although the collection does not contain the files of administrative heads of the Trust, some of their correspondence and inter-office communications can be found in the CRL. The collection does include the files of the Trust's outside counsel, Orran L. Brown.
  - Sub-series 1: Central Records Library
    The Central Records Library 166 boxes and cartons, 3 volumes (75.6 linear feet), contains the official file copies of the Trust's administrative records, 1989 to 1999. The records were assigned numbers and are filed in numerical order, but they also fall into the following thirty-two, sometimes overlapping, subject or form categories: alternative dispute resolution, A.H. Robins, arbitration, bankruptcy, Breland, consummation, contracts, correspondence, final dispute resolution, financial, forms, internal, late Dalkon Shield, litigation, mass mail, McGovern, management reports, newsletters, offer letters, options, orders, other, Other Trust, packets, procedures, projects, releases, settlement conference, special program (for in vitro fertilization), status, trustees, and warning/deadlines. The inventory which follows is in numerical order; available for use in the Special Collections department is an inventory arranged by subject.